Welcome!
This section is called providing great customer service.
The next step that we are going to talk about again in the basic elements of providing customer service is utilizing their expertise.
Now this is easier than said or done but a lot of people who provide customer service don't really realize how many resources they have just at their hands so that they can go ahead and help the customers.
Now as you continue with any business, you are going to learn a lot more about that.
Take your knowledge and share it with the customer.
Any time you can educate your customer and we will speak about this a little bit more in detail later.
Then you are helping that customer better communicate with you what their expectations may be in the future.
You also have a lot of tools available to you as well whether it may be a computer system, maybe you may have data base that you can pull up different information on your customer, maybe you have very specific tools of the trade whether it be a wrench or a hammer or your pen.
Whatever you have that helps you utilize your expertise and communicate that knowledge to your customer is only going to help you assist them in a much much better manner.